And then you connect with your breath and you also stabilize your
Et  puis  tu  prends  contact  avec  ta  respiration  et  tu  stabilises  aussi  les
eyes.
yeux.
You stabilize the eye.
Tu stabilises l'œil.
The eye is an expansion of the brain.
L'œil c'est une expansion du cerveau.
The eye is an expansion of the third ventricle.
L'œil c'est une expansion du troisième ventricule.
And there you are...
Et là tu es...
you breathe
tu respires
you observe the end of the exhalation
tu observes la fin de l'expiration
And you settle into that space that comes after.
Et tu te déposes dans cet espace qu'il y a après.
It's like a bubble you've filled with
C 'est  comme  une  bulle  que  tu  as  remplie  de
emptiness.
vide.
And then you try to stop thinking
Et  puis  tu  essaies  de  terminer  de  penser
about something.
à  quelque  chose.
You could, you think of someone who comes to mind
Tu  pourrais,  tu  penses  à  quelqu 'un  qui  te  vient
like that, to whom you want to send love or kindness, simply.
comme  ça,  à  qui  tu  as  envie  d 'envoyer  de  l 'amour  ou  de  la  bonté,  simplement.
You think of someone to whom you could, through a
Tu  penses  à  quelqu 'un  à  qui  tu  pourrais,  au  travers  d 'une
thought like that, imagine that you can send them well-being,
pensée  comme  ça,  imaginer  que  tu  peux  lui  envoyer  du  bien
tenderness.
-être,  de  la  tendresse.
but you do that
mais tu fais ça
you do that
tu fais ça